<resources>
    <string name="projection_impact">Projection Impact</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="projected_impact">Projected Impact</string>
    <string name="goal_name_placeholder">Goal Name</string>
    <string name="todays_cost">Today’s Cost:</string>
    <string name="future_value">Future Value</string>
    <string name="target">Target</string>
    <string name="monthly_sip">Monthly SIP</string>
    <string name="feasibility_score">Feasibility Score</string>
    <string name="progress">Progress</string>
    <string name="increased_by">Increased By </string>
    <string name="req_monthly">Req.monthly: </string>
    <string name="explore_bundle_goals">Explore Bundle Goals</string>
    <string name="sbi_gold_fund">SBI Gold Fund</string>
    <string name="returns_3y">3Y Returns</string>
    <string name="high_risk_commodities_gold">High Risk . Commodities . Gold</string>
    <string name="invest_now">Invest Now</string>
    <string name="choose_how_to_invest">Choose how to invest</string>
    <string name="select_investment_method">Select an investment method to continue.</string>
    <string name="start_an_sip">Start an SIP</string>
    <string name="sip_description">Automated monthly investments to build wealth steadily over time.</string>
    <string name="start_sip_setup">Start SIP Setup</string>
    <string name="invest_as_lumpsum">Invest as Lump-sum</string>
    <string name="lumpsum_description">Make a one-time investment with your available funds today.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_header">Velvet Investing Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_intro">At Velvet Investing (“Velvet”, “we”, “our”, “us”), we value your trust and are committed to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, share, and safeguard your information when you use our website, mobile application, and related services.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_consent">By accessing or using Velvet Investing, you agree to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_last_updated">Last updated: October 2023</string>

    <string name="pp_section_1_title">1. Information We Collect</string>
    <string name="pp_section_1_a_title">a) Personal Information: </string>
    <string name="pp_section_1_a_content">Full Name, Mobile Number, Email Address, Date of Birth, PAN and other KYC-related information, and bank account details. Even details of payments made for transaction or through our website such as security, expenses, assets, liabilities, goals, and investment preferences.</string>
    <string name="pp_section_1_b_title">b) Technical Information: </string>
    <string name="pp_section_1_b_content">IP address, device type and operating system, browser type, app usage data, log files, Cookies and similar technologies.</string>
    <string name="pp_section_1_c_title">c) Transaction and Service Information: </string>
    <string name="pp_section_1_c_content">Investment instructions, holdings and funds, fixed deposit transaction details, KYC status, Portfolio tracking results, Mutual fund performance, Download history, for report/tax statements.</string>

    <string name="pp_section_2_title">2. How We Use Your Information</string>
    <string name="pp_section_2_intro">We may use your information to:</string>
    <string name="pp_use_item_1">Create and manage your account.</string>
    <string name="pp_use_item_2">Verify your identity and comply with KYC regulations.</string>
    <string name="pp_use_item_3">Provide financial planning, investment, and reporting services.</string>
    <string name="pp_use_item_4">Facilitate mutual fund transactions and manage your portfolio through our licensed partners.</string>
    <string name="pp_use_item_5">Personalize your user experience and provide recommendations.</string>
    <string name="pp_use_item_6">Communicate important updates, offers, news, and account notifications.</string>
    <string name="pp_use_item_7">Analyze platform performance, security, and user experience.</string>
    <string name="pp_use_item_8">Comply with legal obligations, tax, audit, and anti-fraud requirements.</string>

    <string name="pp_section_3_title">3. Legal Basis and Consent</string>
    <string name="pp_section_3_content">Where required, we process your data based on your consent. You can withdraw at any time. In other situations, for compliance with applicable laws, or legitimate business purposes such as fraud prevention, platform security, and service improvement.</string>

    <string name="pp_section_4_title">4. Sharing of Information</string>
    <string name="pp_section_4_intro">We do not sell your personal data. We may share your information only as needed to provide our services with:</string>
    <string name="pp_share_item_1">KYC and identity verification partners.</string>
    <string name="pp_share_item_2">Mutual fund house/AMC, payment, banking, and wealth management partners.</string>
    <string name="pp_share_item_3">CRM, analytics, communication, cloud hosting, and customer support providers.</string>
    <string name="pp_share_item_4">Regulatory bodies or judicial authorities when required by law or as requested.</string>
    <string name="pp_share_item_5">Professional advisors, auditors, or legal consultants under confidentiality agreements.</string>

    <string name="pp_section_5_title">5. Data Storage and Security</string>
    <string name="pp_section_5_content">We maintain reasonable physical, organizational, and administrative safeguards to protect your information against unauthorized access, release, loss, alteration or destruction. Please note that no method of transmission over the internet, or any method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, and we cannot guarantee absolute security.</string>

    <string name="pp_section_6_title">6. Data Retention</string>
    <string name="pp_section_6_content">We retain your information only as long as necessary to provide our services, meet legal obligations, resolve disputes, and support trust.</string>

    <string name="pp_section_7_title">7. Cookies and Tracking Technologies</string>
    <string name="pp_section_7_content">Our website may use cookies to help you adjust to preferred preferences, and analyze traffic.</string>

    <string name="pp_section_8_title">8. Your Rights</string>
    <string name="pp_section_8_content">Subject to applicable law, you have the right to access, correct, or request deletion of your personal data.</string>
    <string name="pp_request_access">Request Access</string>
    <string name="pp_request_delete">Request Delete</string>

    <string name="pp_section_9_title">9. Third-Party Links and Services</string>
    <string name="pp_section_9_content">Our platform may contain links to third-party sites. We are not responsible for their independent policies.</string>

    <string name="pp_section_10_title">10. Children’s Privacy</string>
    <string name="pp_section_10_content">Velvet Investing is for individuals legally eligible for financial services.</string>

    <string name="pp_section_11_title">11. Changes to this Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="pp_section_11_content">We may update this policy. Continued use denotes your acceptance.</string>

    <string name="pp_section_12_title">12. Contact Us</string>
    <string name="pp_contact_name">Velvet Investing</string>
    <string name="pp_contact_email_label">Email</string>
    <string name="pp_contact_email">contact@velvetinvesting.com</string>
    <string name="pp_contact_phone_label">Phone</string>
    <string name="pp_contact_phone">+91 999 001 777, +91 999 001 888</string>
    <string name="pp_contact_office_label">Office</string>
    <string name="pp_contact_office">5th Floor, One Horizon Centre, DLF Phase 5, Golf Course Road, Gurugram, India.</string>

    <string name="terms_conditions_title">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions_header">Welcome to VELVET</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions_intro">These Terms &amp; Conditions govern your use of our application platform, and services. By accessing or using the Platform, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you do not agree, you must not use the Platform.</string>

    <string name="tc_section_1_title">1. Eligibility</string>
    <string name="tc_section_1_content">You must be at least 18 years old and legally able to enter binding contracts to use the Platform. By using the Platform, you confirm you meet these requirements.</string>

    <string name="tc_section_2_title">2. Account Registration</string>
    <string name="tc_section_2_intro">To access certain features, you may need to create an account. You agree to:</string>
    <string name="tc_account_item_1">Provide accurate, complete, and up-to-date information;</string>
    <string name="tc_account_item_2">Keep your login details secure; and</string>
    <string name="tc_account_item_3">Accept responsibility for all activity under your account.</string>
    <string name="tc_section_2_footer">We may suspend or terminate accounts that breach these Terms.</string>

    <string name="tc_section_3_title">3. Licence to Use the Platform</string>
    <string name="tc_section_3_intro">VELVET grants you a limited, non-exclusive, revocable, non-transferable licence to use the Platform for personal or business purposes in accordance with these Terms. You must not:</string>
    <string name="tc_licence_item_1">Copy, distribute, or exploit the Platform or its content;</string>
    <string name="tc_licence_item_2">Use automated tools (bots, scrapers) to access the Platform; or</string>
    <string name="tc_licence_item_3">Interfere with the Platform's functionality.</string>

    <string name="tc_section_4_title">4. Intellectual Property</string>
    <string name="tc_section_4_content">All content, branding, design, software, and materials on the Platform are owned by VELVET or our licensors. You must not copy, modify, or use our intellectual property without written permission.</string>

    <string name="tc_section_5_title">5. User Content</string>
    <string name="tc_section_5_intro">By posting, uploading, or sharing content on the Platform ("User Content"), you:</string>
    <string name="tc_user_content_item_1">Retain ownership of your content;</string>
    <string name="tc_user_content_item_2">Grant VELVET a worldwide, royalty-free, transferable licence to use, reproduce, modify, distribute, display, and communicate your content to operate and promote the Platform; and</string>
    <string name="tc_user_content_item_3">Waive any "moral rights" you may have, meaning you agree not to assert rights against us for adapting or using your content.</string>
    <string name="tc_section_5_footer">You are solely responsible for your User Content. VELVET may remove or disable access to content that breaches these Terms or the law.</string>

    <string name="tc_section_6_title">6. Prohibited Conduct</string>
    <string name="tc_section_6_intro">You must not use the Platform to:</string>
    <string name="tc_prohibited_item_1">Engage in unlawful, harmful, or fraudulent activity;</string>
    <string name="tc_prohibited_item_2">Harass, threaten, or abuse others;</string>
    <string name="tc_prohibited_item_3">Post defamatory, obscene, or misleading content;</string>
    <string name="tc_prohibited_item_4">Disrupt, interfere with, or harm the Platform or its users;</string>
    <string name="tc_prohibited_item_5">Impersonate another person or misrepresent your affiliation; or</string>
    <string name="tc_prohibited_item_6">Violate any laws or third-party rights.</string>

    <string name="tc_section_12_title">12. Breach &amp; Termination</string>
    <string name="tc_section_12_content">We may, at our discretion and without notice, suspend, restrict, or terminate your access to the Platform if you breach these Terms, misuse the Platform, or act in a way that harms VELVET or other users. You may stop using the Platform at any time.</string>
</resources>